Guide to the Brooklyn Ephemera Collection BCMS.0007
Brooklyn Collection
- Churches: Grace Church (Episcopal) (Box 7)
- Churches: Grace Gospel Church (Box 7)
- Churches: Grace Presbyterian (Box 7)
- Churches: Grace Reformed Church of Flatbush (Box 7)
- Churches: Grace United Methodist Church (Box 7)
- Churches: Gravesend Reformed (Box 7)
- Churches: Greenwood Baptist Church (Box 7)
- Churches: Hanson Place Methodist (Box 7)
- Churches: Hanson Place Seventh Day Adventist (Box 7)
- Churches: Holy Cross Roman Catholic (Box 7)
- Churches: Jane's (Methodist) (Box 7)
- Churches: King's Highway Congregational (Box 7)
- Churches: Lafayette Avenue (Presbyterian) (Box 7)
- Churches: Lefferts Park Baptist (Box 7)
- Churches: Marcy Avenue Baptist (Box 7)
- Churches: Messiah (Protestant Episcopal) (Box 7)
- Churches: Methodism: Journal of the New York East Conference (Box 7)
- Churches: Miscellaneous (Box 7)
- Churches: New Utrecht Reformed Church pamphlets, 1937, 1952 (Box 7)
- Churches: Our Lady of Consolation (Box 7)
- Churches: Our Lady of Good Counsel (Box 7)
- Churches: Our Lady of Loreto (Box 7)
- Churches: Our Lady of Lourdes (Box 7)
- Churches: Our Lady of Mercy (Box 7)
- Churches: Our Lady of Perpetual Help (Box 7)
- Churches: Parkville Congregational Church (Box 7)
- Churches: Plymouth Church of Pilgrims (United Church of Christ) (Box 7)
- Churches: Presbyterian General (Box 7)
- Churches: Prospect Avenue Methodist Episcopal Church (Box 7)
- Churches: Redeemer (Baptist) (Box 7)
- Churches: Redeemer (Episcopal) (Box 7)
- Churches: Redemption Church of Christ (Box 7)
- Churches: Reformed General (Box 7)
- Churches: Regina Pacis Votive Shrine (Box 7)
- Churches: Salem Baptist (Box 7)
- Churches: Salem Danish (Lutheran) (Box 7)
- Churches: Simpson (Methodist Episcopal) (Box 7)
- Churches: Sixth Avenue (Methodist Episcopal) (Box 7)
- Churches: South (Congregational) (Box 7)
- Churches: South Third Street (Presbyterian) (Box 7)
- Churches: Spencer Memorial Church (Presbyterian) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Agnes (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Ann's Episcopal (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Athanasius Church (Roman Catholic) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Augustine's Church (Episcopal) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Bartholomew (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Bernadette (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Catherine of Alexandria, V.M. (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Frances de Chantal (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Francis of Assisi (Box 7)
- Churches: St. George's (Protestant Episcopal) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Grace Protestant Chapel (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Ignatius (Box 7)
- Churches: St. James (Protestant Episcopal) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. John's (Episcopal) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. John's the Evangelist (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Luke & St. Mathew (Episcopal) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Luke's (Lutheran) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Mark's (Methodist) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Mark's Congregational Church (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Mary's (Episcopal) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Mathew's (Lutheran) [Canarsie] (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Mathew's (Lutheran) [Park Slope] (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Paul's (Episcopal) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Paul's (Methodist Episcopal) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Paul's (Protestant Episcopal) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Paul's (Swedish Lutheran) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Peter's (Episcopal) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Peter's (German Evangelical Lutheran) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Stephen's (Lutheran) (Box 7)
- Churches: St. Thomas's (Protestant Episcopal) (Box 7)
- Churches: Sunday School (Box 7)
- Churches: Trinity Holy Church (Box 7)
- Churches: Twelfth Street Reformed (Box 7)
- Churches: Union Baptist Church (Box 7)
- Churches: Union of Bay Ridge (Presbyterian) (Box 7)
- Churches: Washington Avenue Baptist Church (Box 7)
- Churches: Westminster United Presbyterian Church (Box 7)
- Citizens Budget Commission: Annual Reports and Press Releases (Box 7)
- Citizens Union (Box 7)
- Civic Center: Master Plan (Box 7)
- Civil Defense: Annual Reports and Manuals [2 folders] (Box 7)
- Clinton Hill (Box 7)
- Clubs: Amersfort Council, Order of United American Mechanics (Box 7)
- Clubs: Anvil Chorus (Box 7)
- Clubs: Apollo Club (Box 7)
- Clubs: Assembly Regular Club (Box 7)
- Clubs: Atlantic Yacht Club (Box 7, Box 16)
- Clubs: Aurora Grata Club (Box 7)
- Clubs: B.P.O. Elks: Brooklyn Lodge No. 22 (Box 7)
- Clubs: Blessed Sacrament Club (Box 7)
- Clubs: Brooklyn Bird Club (Box 7)
- Clubs: Brooklyn Camera Club [2 folders] (Box 7)
- Clubs: Brooklyn Club (Box 7)
- Clubs: Brooklyn League (Box 7)
- Clubs: Brooklyn Negro Civic Corporation (Box 7)
- Clubs: Brooklyn Poetry Circle (Box 7)
- Clubs: Brooklyn Revenue Reform Club (Box 7)
- Clubs: Brooklyn Riding Club (Box 7)
- Clubs: Brooklyn Rowing Club (Box 7)
- Clubs: Brooklyn Single Tax Club (Box 7)
- Clubs: Brooklyn Women's Club (Box 7)
- Clubs: Brooklyn Young Republicans Club (Box 7)
- Clubs: Congress of West Indian American Organizations (Box 7)
- Clubs: Cortelyou Club (Box 7)
- Clubs: Court Gravesend (Box 7)
- Clubs: Crescent Athletic Club (Box 7)
- Clubs: East Brooklyn Union Campaign Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: East Midwood Civic Association (Box 8)
- Clubs: Franklin Literary Society (Box 8)
- Clubs: Friendly Sons of St. Patrick (Box 8)
- Clubs: Germania Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: Grand Army of the Republic (Box 8)
- Clubs: Hamilton Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: Hanover Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: International Order of Odd Fellows (Amersfort Council) (Box 8)
- Clubs: Invincible Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: Kings County Democratic Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: Kings County Medical Society (Box 8)
- Clubs: Knickerbocker Field Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: Laurence Social Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: Masonic [2 folders] (Box 8)
- Clubs: Membership cards – Betts Family, 1896-1945 (Box 8)
- Clubs: Midwood Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: Montauk Club [2 folders] (Box 8)
- Clubs: Mrs. Field's Literary Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: Municipal Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: National Association of Negro Business and Professional Women's Clubs, Brooklyn Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: National Provident Union (Box 8)
- Clubs: New England Society in the City of Brooklyn (Box 8)
- Clubs: New Utrecht Liberty Pole Association (Box 8)
- Clubs: New York Civil Liberties Union Brooklyn Chapter (Box 8)
- Clubs: Osborne Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: Oxford Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: Rembrandt Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: Rhodes, John W. Social Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: Riding and Driving Club of Brooklyn (Box 8)
- Clubs: Rotary Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: Seidl Society (Box 8)
- Clubs: Society of Old Brooklynites (Box 8)
- Clubs: South Brooklyn Community Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: St. Nicholas Society (Box 8)
- Clubs: St. Patrick Society (Box 8)
- Clubs: Union Course Civil Association (Box 8)
- Clubs: Union League Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: Unionists' Association (Box 8)
- Clubs: Utrecht Council (Box 8)
- Clubs: Williamsburg Luncheon Club (Box 8)
- Clubs: Wings Club Yearbook, 1950-1951 (Box 8)
- Cobble Hill (Box 8)
- Committee for the Erection of a Veteran's Hospital (Box 8)
- Coney Island: General [5 folders] (Box 8, Box 16, Box OS 7)
- Coney Island: Improvement Ground Breaking Ceremony (Box 8)
- Coney Island: New York Aquarium (Box 8)
- Correspondence (Box 8)
- County Clerks Office (Box 8)
- Courts: Appellate Division, Supreme Court (Box 8)
- Courts: Court of Special sessions of the City of New York (Annual Report) (Box 8)
- Courts: Domestic Relations Court Reports (Box 8)
- Courts: Judicial Statistics (Box 8)
- Courts: Kings County Circuit Court (Box 8)
- Courts: Kings County Grand Jurors Association (Box 8)
- Courts: Supreme Court Kings County (Box 8)
- Crown Heights (Box 8)
- Dances & Parties: Fliers (Box 8)
- Dances & Parties: Invitations, Programs, and Menus (Box 8)
- Day Care Agencies (Box 8)
- Department of Finance (Box 8)
- Department of Health (Box 8)
- Diocese of Long Island (Box 8)
- Docks & Piers: New York Dock Co. (Box 8)
- Docks & Piers: Reports, 1950-1952 (Box 8)
- Docks & Piers: Views (Box 8)
- Domestic Life (Box 9)
- Downtown Brooklyn (Box 9, Box 16)
- Drugs: Report: Committee on Use of Narcotics Among Teen Age Youth, 1951 (Box 9)
- Drugs: Report: Mayor's Committee on Drug Addiction, 1951 (Box 9)
- Dumbo (Box 9)
- East New York (Box 9)
- Eastern Parkway (Box 9)
- Ebbets Field (Box 9)
- Elections & Campaigns (Box 9)
- Factories: American Sugar Refinery (Box 9)
- Factories: Benjamin Moore Paint Factory (Box 9)
- Factories: Brooklyn Flint Glass Works (Box 9)
- Factories: Consolidated Macaroni (Box 9)
- Factories: Demaco (Box 9)
- Factories: E. Greenfield's Son & Co. (candy) (Box 9)
- Factories: Jennings Lace Works (Box 9)
- Factories: Refined Macaroni (Box 9)
- Ferries: Fulton (Box 9)
- Fire Department: Fire Engines (Box 9)
- Fire Department: General (Box 9)
- Firemen: Volunteer (Box 9)
- Flatbush: Brooklyn's Garden, 1908 (Box 9)
- Flatbush: Flatbush Avenue (Box 9)
- Flatbush: Flatbush Historical Society [2 folders] (Box 9)
- Flatbush: Flatbush Neighborhood Manhattan Terrace (Box 9)
- Flatbush: Flatbush-Nostrand Chamber of Commerce (Box 9)
- Flatbush: General (Box 9, Box 16)
- Flatbush: Houses (Box 9)
- Fort Greene (Box 9)
- Fort Hamilton (Box 9)
- Fulton Street Businesses: Photographers (Box 9)
- Gateway National Recreation Area (Box 9)
- Gay Communities (Box 9)
- Genealogy (Box 9)
- Gerritsen Beach (Box 9)
- Gold Mines & Mining (Williamsburgh) (Box 9)
- Governor's Island (Box 9)
- Gowanus: Gowanus Bay (Box 9)
- Gowanus: Gowanus Canal (Box 9, Box 16)
- Gowanus: Gowanus Canal: Aerial Survey (Box 9)
- Gowanus: General (Box 9)
- Gowanus: Homes: Old Stone House (Box 9)
- Gowanus: Miss Gowanus [facsimile of artist's book], 1996 (Box 9)
- Grand Army Plaza: Design Trust for Public Space (Box 9)
- Grand Army Plaza: General (Box 9)
- Gravesend: General (Box 9)
- Gravesend: Homes: Lake House (Box 9)
- Gravesend: Homes: Van Sicklen House (Box 9)
- Gravesend: Hook & Ladder (Box 9)
- Greenpoint: General (Box 9)
- Greenpoint: Homes: Peter Cooper's Row (Box 9)
- Greenwood Cemetery (Box 9)
- Hall of Records (Box 9)
- Heart of Brooklyn (Box 9)
- History: Civil War (Box 9)
- History: Dutch (Box 9)
- History: Revolution: Battle of Brooklyn [2 folders] (Box 9, Box 16)
- History: Revolution: Battle of Long Island (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Beth Moses Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Beth-El Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Brookdale Hospital Medical Center (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Brooklyn Cancer Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Brooklyn Eye & Ear Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Brooklyn Home for Consumptives (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Brooklyn Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Brooklyn Jewish Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Brooklyn State Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Coney Island Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Fort Hamilton Veteran's Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Jewish Hospital of Brooklyn (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Jewish Sanitarium Hospital for Chronic Diseases (Box 9)
- Hospitals: King's County Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Kingston Avenue Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Long Island College Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Methodist Episcopal Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Norwegian Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: St. Charles Orthopedic (Box 9)
- Hospitals: St. Mary's Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: St. Peter's Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: William McKinley Memorial Hospital (Box 9)
- Hospitals: Williamsburg Pediatric Specialty Center (Schneider Children's Hospital) (Box 9)
- Hotels: Bossert Hotel (Box 9)
- Hotels: Brighton Beach Hotel (Box 9)
- Hotels: General (Box 9)
- Hotels: Hotel Mohawk (Box 9)
- Hotels: Hotel St. George (Box 9)
- Houses: General (Box 9)
- Houses: Martense Homestead (Box 9)
- Housing: Brownsville (Box 9)
- Housing: Concord Village Project (Box 9)
- Housing: Cooper Park Houses (Box 9)
- Housing: Fort Greene (Box 10)
- Housing: General (Box 10)
- Housing: Gowanus Houses (Box 10)
- Housing: Grand Jury Fire Investigation, 1953 (Box 10)
- Housing: Howard Houses (Box 10)
- Housing: Jamaica Bay Emergency (Box 10)
- Housing: Riverside Buildings (Box 10)
- Housing: Van Dyke Houses (Box 10)
- Housing: Wallabout Houses (Box 10)
- Indigenous People: Land Acknowledgement (Box 10)
- Internal Revenue Service (Box 10)
- Invitations and Greeting Cards: Bar Mitzvahs (Box 10)
- Invitations and Greeting Cards: Holidays (Box 10)
- Invitations and Greeting Cards: Weddings (Box 10)
- Juvenile Aid Bureau: Police and children (Box 10)
- Juvenile Delinquency (Box 10)
- Kings County Penitentiary (Box 10)
- Labor Unions: Building Trades Employers' Association (Box 10)
- Labor Unions: Empire Protective Association (Box 10)
- Landmarks Preservation Commission (Box 10)
- Lefferts Manor Association (Box 10)
- Lefferts Manor Association: History of Community [No Photocopying], 1938 March (Box 10)
- Letters: A letter to Gertrude Mendelson, mother of Wilfred (Mendy) Mendelson (Box 10)
- Liquor Industry: Old Williamsburg Whiskey (Box OS 4)
- Litchfield Villa (Box 10)
- Long Island Association (Box 10)
- Long Island Historical Society [now Brooklyn Historical Society] (Box 10)
- Maps: Old Breukelen & New (Brooklyn Daily Eagle), 1946 (Box 10)
- Maps: Brooklyn Eagle War Map, 1904 (Box 10)
- Maps: General (Box 10)
- Maps: Neighborhood Guides (Box 10)
- Marine Park (Box 10)
- Markets: Wallabout Market (Box 10)
- Memorials: Memorial at Verdun (Box 10)
- Menus: Alumni Association of Boys High School (Box 10)
- Menus: Ben Maksik's Roadside (Box 10)
- Menus: Brooklyn Eagle Home Guild (Box 10)
- Menus: Brooklyn Union Gas Co. Dinner (Box 10)
- Menus: Café Troy (Box 10)
- Menus: Cairo Inn (Box 10)
- Menus: Candlelight Restaurant (Box 10)
- Menus: Chicken Delight (Box 10)
- Menus: Citizens of Brooklyn, Auspices of the Brooklyn League (Box 10)
- Menus: Clam Bar and Restaurant (Box 10)
- Menus: Company 'C' 13th Regiment (Box 10)
- Menus: Cooky's Steak Pubs Inc. (Box 10)
- Menus: Embassy Club (Box 10)
- Menus: Executive Dinner Tours (Box 10)
- Menus: F.W.I.L. Lundy Bros. (Box 10)
- Menus: Feltmans Arcade Restaurant (Box 10)
- Menus: Flavia Seafood (Box 10)
- Menus: Foffe Restaurant (Box 10)
- Menus: Gage and Tollner (Box 10)
- Menus: General (Box 10)
- Menus: Golden Nut Restaurant (Box 10)
- Menus: Hettel's Steaks and Chops (Box 10)
- Menus: Hotel Touraine (Box 10)
- Menus: J. & M. Restaurant (Box 16)
- Menus: Kiefer Catering Co. (Box 10)
- Menus: Lane's Original Irish House (Box 10)
- Menus: Lassen & Hennigs (Box 10)
- Menus: Lichee Nut (Box 10)
- Menus: McGinnis of Sheepshead Bay (Box 16)
- Menus: Merit Farms (Box 10)
- Menus: Montauk Club (Box 10)
- Menus: Municipal Club of Brooklyn (Box 10)
- Menus: Nanatori (Box 10)
- Menus: Non Brooklyn Restaurants (Box 10)
- Menus: Officers of the 14th Regiment and col. Herman Metz (Box 16)
- Menus: Otjen's Restaurant and Sea Grill (Box 16)
- Menus: Pizza Dee-Lite (Box 10)
- Menus: Prospect Heights Citizens Association (Box 10)
- Menus: Receiving Ship at New York (Box 10)
- Menus: Savoy (Box 10, Box 16)
- Menus: Talmud Torah Aitz Chaim (Box 10)
- Menus: Tang's (Box 10)
- Menus: Testimony Dinner for Archbishop Thomas Molloy (Box 10)
- Menus: United States Coast Guard Brooklyn Barracks (Box 10)
- Menus: Veteran Association of the 13th Regiment (Box 10)
- Menus: Villepigue's Inn (Box 10)
- Midwood: General (Box 10)
- Migration Internal (Box 10)
- Military (Box 10)
- Mill Basin: Harbor (Box 10)
- Mill Basin: Schenck Homestead (Box 10)
- Miss Brooklyn Beauty Contest (Box 10)
- Monasteries and Convents (Box 10)
- Monitor (Box 10)
- Motion Picture Industry (Film) (Box 10)
- Movies: Brooklyn Bridge Script (Box 10)
- Movies: Posters (Cabinet Morgue Flat File 1, Drawer 21)
- Municipal Building (Box 10)
- Museums: Brooklyn Children's Museum (Box 10)
- Museums: Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences: "Our Brooklyn" by Ralph Foster Weld, 1940 (Box 10)
- Museums: Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences: Edward S. Curtis Lecture (Box 10)
- Museums: Brooklyn Institute of Arts and Sciences: General (Box 10)
- Museums: Brooklyn Museum: Brooklyn Artists (Box 10)
- Museums: Brooklyn Museum: Community Gallery (Box 10)
- Museums: Brooklyn Museum: General (Box 10)
- Museums: Eden Musee (Box 10)
- Museums: General (Box 11)
- Museums: Greenpoint Monitor Museum (Box OS 3)
- Museums: Whitney Museum of American Art, New York City (Box 11)
- Newkirk Avenue (Box 11)
- Newsletters: A & S Spotlight (Box 11)
- Newsletters: American Hebrew and Jewish Messenger (Box OS 3)
- Newsletters: The Avonian (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Bedford Stuyvesant Little League News (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Brooklyn Alliance of Neighborhood Gardens (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Brooklyn Bugle (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Brooklyn College Staff (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Brooklyn Daily Programme (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Brooklyn Daily Stage (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Brooklyn Heights News (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Brooklyn Junior League Club (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Brooklyn Musical Monthly (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Brooklyn Navy Yard Shipworker (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Brooklyn Post Office (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Brooklyn Stage (Box 11)
- Newsletters: The Brownstoner (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Brownsville Counsellor (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Fort Greene Observer (Box 11)
- Newsletters: The Hill (Clinton Hill) [3 folders] (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Italian American Review (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Kings County Grand Juror (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Long Island University News (Box 11)
- Newsletters: New York City Housing Authority Management Newsletter (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Park Slope Fifth Avenue Committee (Box 11)
- Newsletters: The Spirit of Flatbush (Box 11)
- Newsletters: The Third Rail (Box 11)
- Newsletters: Wash Ave (Washington Avenue-Prospect Heights Association) (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Astella Action News (Box OS 1)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Atlantic Currents (Box OS 1)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Bay Ridge Cannoneer (Box 16)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Brill Magazine (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Brooklyn Daily (Box 16)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Brooklyn Heights Press and Cobble Hill News (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: The Brooklyn Journal of Arts and Urban Affairs [supplement to Brooklyn Heights Press] (Box OS 2)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Brooklyn Teacher (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Brooklyn, The Different Digest (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Brooklyn's Happening (Box OS 1)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Brooklyn Progress Supplement (Box OS 1)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Brownstone News (Box OS 1)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Business Week (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: The Carroll Gardens Cobble Hill Newspaper (Box OS 1)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Crain's New York Business [special Brooklyn Market Focus] (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: The Fort Greene Paper (Box OS 2)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Fund Raiser (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: General [2 folders] (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Heinrich's Floral Instructor (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: L Magazine (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Manhattan Beach Sun (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Midwood Sentry (Box OS 1)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Myrtle Avenue News (Box OS 1)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Neighbors and Merchants/ Vecinos and Comerciantes (Box OS 1)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Newsday Magazine (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: New York Herald Tribune (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: New York News Magazine (Box OS 3)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: New York Sunday News (Box 16)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Newsday Magazine (Box 11, Box OS 3)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: NRG Magazine (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Park Slope Reader (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Phoenix Brownstone Guide (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Prattfolio, the magazine of Pratt Institute (Box 16)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Progress (Box OS 1)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Red Hook News (Box OS 1)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: South Brooklyn News (Box OS 1)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Spring 3100 (Box 11)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: T & F. Echo (Box 16)
- Newspapers & Periodicals: Williamsburg Advocate (Box OS 1)
- New Utrecht: Homes: Van Pelt Manor (Box 11)
- New York City [2 folders] (Box 11)
- New York City: Inaugural Ceremonies, 2002 (Box 11)
- New York City: Public Development Corporation: Brooklyn (Box 11)
- New York City: Transit Authority (Box 11)
- New York Public Library (Box 11)
- Office Buildings: Central Building (Box 11)
- Office Buildings: Old Sun Building (Box 11)
- Old Town Records (Box 11)
- Organizations: American Institute of Architects (Box 11)
- Organizations: American Red Cross (Box 11)
- Organizations: Ancient Order of Hibernians (Box 11)
- Organizations: Bedford-Stuyvesant Beautification Association (Box 11)
- Organizations: Bedford-Stuyvesant Restoration Corporation (Box 11)
- Organizations: Better Brooklyn Committee (Box 16)
- Organizations: Black American Roots Society (Box 11)
- Organizations: Brooklyn Art Association (Box 11)
- Organizations: Brooklyn Athletic Association (Box 11)
- Organizations: Brooklyn Art Guild (Box 11)
- Organizations: Brooklyn Arts Council (Box 11)
- Organizations: Brooklyn Employee's Association (Box 11)
- Organizations: Brooklyn Library Council (Box 11)
- Organizations: Brooklyn Sunday School Union (Box 11)
- Organizations: Brownstone Revival Coalition (Box 11)
- Organizations: Community Boards (Box 11)
- Organizations: General (Box 11)
- Organizations: Greek Letter Societies Phi Sigma Chi (Box 11)
- Organizations: Greensward Foundation, Inc. (Box 11)
- Organizations: Hadassah Central, Brooklyn Chapter (Box 11)
- Organizations: Heart of Brooklyn (Box 11)
- Organizations: Homecrest Community Services (Box 11)
- Organizations: International Brick Collectors' Association (Box 11)
- Organizations: Italian Historical Society of America (Box 11)
- Organizations: Italian Mutual Aid Society Flower of Boro Park, Inc. (Box 11)
- Organizations: Knights of Temperance (Box 11)
- Organizations: Magnolia Tree Earth Center of Bedford-Stuyvesant, Inc. (Box 11)
- Organizations: Medical: General (Box 11)
- Organizations: Medical: Brooklyn Tuberculosis & Respiratory Disease Association (Box 11)
- Organizations: Medical Society of the County of Kings (Box 11)
- Organizations: New York Library Club (Box 11)
- Organizations: Prospect Lefferts Gardens Neighborhood Association (Box 11)
- Organizations: Society of Architectural Historians (Box 12)
- Organizations: Sorosis (Box 12)
- Organizations: Triangle Parks Flatbush Avenue Improvement Committee (Box 12)
- Organizations: Triple Canopy (Box 12)
- Organizations: United Boys Brigade of America (Box 12)
- Organizations: United Nations Association of Brooklyn (Box 12)
- Organizations: United Regular Democratic Organization (Box 12)
- Organizations: United States Naval Armed Guard Center (Box 12)
- Organizations: Visiting Nurse Association of Brooklyn (Box 12)
- Organizations: Wyckoff House and Association (Box 12)
- Organizations: YMCA [2 folders] (Box 12)
- Organizations: YMCA: Prospect Park Branch (Box 12)
- Organizations: Youth Organizations (Box 12)
- Organizations: YWCA (Box 12)
- Park Slope (Box 12)
- Parks: Brooklyn Bridge Park (Box 12, Box OS 3)
- Parks: Canarsie Pier (Box 12)
- Parks: Dyker Beach (Box 12)
- Parks: Fort Greene (Box 12)
- Parks: General (Box 12, Box OS 6)
- Parks: Prospect Park: Pre-1960s (Box 12)
- Parks: Prospect Park: 1960s (Box 12)
- Parks: Prospect Park: Post-1960s (Box 12)
- Pets (Box 12)
- Politics: Badillo, Herman (Box 12)
- Politics: Campaigns (Box 12, Box OS 3)
- Politics: Central Brooklyn Mobilization for Political Action (Box 12)
- Politics: Communist Party (Box 12)
- Politics: Independent Progressive Politics Network (Box 12)
- Politics: Low, Seth (Box 12)
- Politics: Mailer / Breslin (Box 12)
- Politics: Millman, Joan (Box 12)
- Politics: NY State (Box 12)
- Politics: Progressive Labor Party (Box 12)
- Politics: Revolutionary Youth League (Box 12)
- Politics: United Taxpayers Party (Box 12)
- Population: New York City's Population Growth, 1790-1970 (Box 12)
- Portraits: Beecher, Henry Ward (Box 12)
- Portraits: Buchalter, Louis (Box 12)
- Portraits: Corse Payton Theatre Company (Box 12)